(Leonard:)So, what's going on with Raj?
(Howard:)Well, the good news
is he has no problem...
...with my mother's tur-briska-fil.
(Penny:)Hard to believe, but go on.
(Howard:)The bad news
is he says he's getting deported.
(Leonard:)What do you mean
he's getting deported?
I believe it means the U.S. government
is going to expel him from the country.
He could return to India, immigrate to
another country willing to accept him...
(Sheldon:)...or wander the high seas
as a stateless pirate.
(Sheldon:)Personally, I'd choose pirate.
(Howard:)Penny, would you mind stepping outside
so we can speak to him?
(Penny:)Ugh. Fine, but the man really needs to work
on his girl issues.
(Sheldon:)Another reason
to consider a life of piracy.
(Sheldon:)Even today, I understand
that's an all-male profession.
(Howard:)Okay, she's gone.
(Raj:)Sorry I lost my cool.